<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post on StyleThief</title><link>https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/tags/post/</link><description>Recent content in Post on StyleThief</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Emma Lee</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:50:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/tags/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WIP: Design History Tracker</title><link>https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/wip-design-history-tracker/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/wip-design-history-tracker/</guid><description>WIP: Design History Tracker 🚨 Upcoming Feature Alert! 🚨 Say hello to our upcoming feature: the Design History Tracker. Soon, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to effortlessly monitor the evolution of design trends on your favorite websites.
Handpick sites to watch, and let StyleThief do the rest. From font changes to layout tweaks, our Design History Tracker logs every detail, giving you valuable insights into design patterns and trends over time. Use these analytics for market research, or just to stay updated on current trends!</description></item><item><title>WIP: Figma Integration</title><link>https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/wip-figma-integration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/wip-figma-integration/</guid><description>WIP: Figma Integration 🎉 Exciting Announcement! 🎉 We are thrilled to announce that StyleThief will soon be integratable with Figma, the leading design collaboration platform!
With this integration, designers can seamlessly import collected design assets and styles directly from StyleThief into their Figma projects. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s fonts, colors, or CSS snippets, bridging the gap between StyleThief and Figma empowers designers to streamline their workflows, enhance collaboration, and bring their creative visions to life with unparalleled efficiency.</description></item><item><title>WIP: Hoverable Analyzer</title><link>https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/wip-hoverable-analyzer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emmrlee.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/wip-hoverable-analyzer/</guid><description>WIP: Hoverable Analyzer 🚀 Hoverable Analyzer is Coming Soon! 🚀 The team at StyleThief is working hard to bring you a new way to &amp;ldquo;steal&amp;rdquo; inspirational design assets from your favorite websites.
With the Hoverable Analyzer, you will soon be able to simply hover over any font, color, or element on a webpage, and instantly reveal detailed information about its styling. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re seeking inspiration or assessing design elements, the Hoverable Analyzer empowers you to gather insights and spark creativity in the blink of an eye.</description></item></channel></rss>